[
    {
      "question": "What is the HTML tag under which one can write the JavaScript code?",
      "choice1": "<script>",
      "choice2": "<scripted>",
      "choice3": "<js>",
      "choice4": "<javascript>",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct syntax for referring to an external script called 'main.js'?",
      "choice1": "<script href='main.js'>",
      "choice2": "<script name='main.js'>",
      "choice3": "<script src='main.js'>",
      "choice4": "<script file='main.js'>",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the correct syntax to display “Hello World” in an alert box?",
      "choice1": "msgBox('Hello World');",
      "choice2": "alertBox('Hello World');",
      "choice3": "msg('Hello World');",
      "choice4": "alert('Hello World');",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the syntax for creating a function in JavaScript named as myFunction?",
        "choice1": "function = myFunction()",
        "choice2": "function myFunction()",
        "choice3": "function : myFunction()",
        "choice4": "function: = myFunction() ",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How is the function called in JavaScript?",
        "choice1": "call myFunction();",
        "choice2": "call function myFunction();",
        "choice3": "myFunction();",
        "choice4": "function myFunction();",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "How to write an ‘if’ statement for executing some code. If “i” is NOT equal to 5?",
        "choice1": "if(i<>5)",
        "choice2": "if i<>5",
        "choice3": "if(i!=5)",
        "choice4": "if i!=5",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the correct syntax for adding comments in JavaScript?",
        "choice1": " <!–-This is a comment-->",
        "choice2": "//This is a comment",
        "choice3": "–This is a comment",
        "choice4": "**This is a comment**",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "How to initialize an array in JavaScript?",
        "choice1": "var userNames = 'John', 'Robert', 'Michael'",
        "choice2": "var userNames = (1=John, 2=Robert, 3=Michael)",
        "choice3": "var userNames = {1:'John', 2:'Robert, 3:'Michael'}",
        "choice4": "var userNames = ['John', 'Robert', 'Michael']",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": " What is the JavaScript syntax for printing values in Console?",
        "choice1": " print(5)",
        "choice2": "console.log(5)",
        "choice3": "console.print(5)",
        "choice4": "console(5)",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the method in JavaScript used to remove the whitespace at the beginning and end of any string?",
        "choice1": "strip()",
        "choice2": "trim()",
        "choice3": "stripped()",
        "choice4": "trimmed()",
        "answer": 2
    }

  ]